I’m so scared.
[WONBIN, I found you!]
[SHOTARO waiting for the elevator in the basement.]
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Please, hurry!
[Takes the elevator up to the 4th floor.]
Their screaming sound...
Why can’t they hide themselves well?
[WONBIN arrives in prison.]
[Methods to escape prison and
member’s contact list.]
[If you don’t escape the prison within 20 minutes,
you are locked up until the game is over.]
Wait a minute, I just need to be clever in order to win this.
I have two keys right now.
[One from the elevator.]
[← The tree where the key was hanging.]
[One from the flower bed where the seeker was.]
[WONBIN already found two keys.]
There’s only 3,187 seconds left.
But there’s no reason to
leave right now.
Someone got captured.
Oh!
That scared me.
Woah.
Is there somewhere to hide here?
Oh, here!
I guess I can enter here.
There’s no way I’ll get caught in here.
[SHOTARO hiding in the bathroom.]
But I can’t stay still.
[Goes back out again.]
[Sound of the elevator arriving.]
I heard the sound of the elevator.
[EUNSEOK, SHOTARO and the seeker are located on the 3rd floor.]
[The seeker got out of the elevator.]
This is quite a thriller.
It is quite a thriller, everyone.
You don’t know when you’ll get captured so
you’re always nervous
and anxious.
Should I go out or not?
[Phone alarm goes off.]
[Hint for the key.]
[Laundry room on the 4th floor.]
Hint for the remaining keys, the laundry room on the 4th floor.
Oh! It’s here!
Laundry room on the
4th floor.
[Heads to the hallway after checking the message.]
[SHOTARO, I found you!]
[EUNSEOK hiding on the same floor as SHOTARO.]
This is crazy.
Am I getting captured?
Look, if you don’t escape the prison within 20 minutes,
you’re locked up until the game is over.
There’s no reason to keep going out there and getting caught by the seeker.
That’s true.
The remaining time is 2,778 seconds.
I have two keys.
[Trying their best to stay locked up.]
[The seeker is still on the 4th floor.]
[EUNSEOK and the seeker are located on the 3rd floor.]
[← EUNSEOK]
It's in front of me.
On the same floor. On the same floor.
(Light goes off.)
[EUNSEOK, I found you!]
Hello.
Ah...
How did you know I was in here?
[One of your members has been captured and sent to prison.
Current survival rate is 50%.]
Who is it? Who got captured?
More than 50% has to be alive
in order for BRIIZE to receive a gift…
SHOTARO, why aren’t you leaving?
I will.
Can you leave?
I got the key from WONBIN.
Hurry! You need to hurry and leave.
One person needs to leave now.
I know.
So, hurry up and leave.
Please, rescue me.
Who has a key?
You have one and
I have this one.
SOHEE may have used one.
SOHEE used one?
SUNGCHAN is the only one who has a key.
SUNGCHAN has a key?
Yes.
I used SUNGCHAN’s key
in order to rescue SOHEE earlier.
[ 4 keys found and
2 of them are already used.]
Ah...ANTON.
ANTON is still hiding in the same place.
Call ANTON right now.
But do we have to go find the remaining keys?
Do we need to find the other keys?
Do we need to
find the remaining keys?
The remaining keys are
on the 3rd and 4th floor.
[Hint for the key.]
[The laundry room on the 4th floor & Room 308 on the 3rd floor.
Who has
the other keys?
First, I’m going to hide.
Our team members,
except for ANTON,
are active in searching for the keys.
I think ANTON and I will just
stay put
and hide for the rest of the game.
Was I locked up here for 20 minutes?
I want to come out now.
[Phone alarm goes off.]
A message came.
A message came?
[A few minutes later, when the time is ]
[2,222 seconds,]
[the seeker will disappear]
[and you will be given four minutes to hide yourselves again.]
[After four minutes, there will be two seekers so]
[prepare yourselves and hide very well.]
There are going to be two seekers?
It’s okay, I won’t get caught if I stay here.
I hope so...
Ah really? Two seekers?
Should I just stay in prison?
You’re out?
Yeah, I got out.
I’m going to come out when it hits 2,222 seconds.
[The seeker disappears.]
[Only RIIZE remains in the building.]
[The seeker reappears.]
Do I have to try hard for 4 minutes to
hide myself?
Do I have to go look for the keys?
Ha… should I just stay here?
This is the best choice…
I'm leaving.
But… two seekers are a bit challenging.
[WONBIN using the elevator to relocate.]
Then I should hurry and find the keys.
[SUNGCHAN is also searching for the keys.]
[The seeker reappears.]
[← SUNGCHAN] [← WONBIN]
[Joins WONBIN on 3rd floor.]
Room 308.
Aaaargh!
Oh? You’re alive?
Yea, I’m alive.
Did you find the key?
WONBIN saved me but the key isn’t here.
This is the location according to the hint.
[Hint for the key.]
[Room 308.]
The 4th floor.
Did you go to the 4th floor (location of the hint)?
[The seeker reappears.]
[SHOTARO obtains the key underneath the bed.]
I found it.
You found it!
Let’s go to the 4th floor now.
Hurry, hurry! Let’s go to the 4th floor!
[Hint for the key.]
[The laundry room on the 4th floor.]
The laundry room!
[SOHEE’s phone ringing.]
[At the same time in the basement cafeteria.]
Hello? Hello?
Who is this?
Do you have a key, SOHEE?
I have one!
You do?
I do. I do.
I'm locked up right now.
You want me to rescue you?
Yup.
Okay, fine. Just hold on tight for a bit.
[The seeker reappears.]
[SOHEE hiding in the corner of the cafeteria.]
[Heads to the prison right next door.]
[The seeker reappears.]
Please save EUNSEOK.
I’m going now.
Okay, thank you.
[Returns to position after completing the mission. ]
I’m back.
[The seeker reappears.]
Thank you.
[The seeker returns in less than a minute and
EUNSEOK successfully escapes from prison.]
[On the 4th floor, members are eagerly looking for the key.]
The washroom.
Is it the washroom?
It’s the laundry room, right?
The laundry room is right here!
This is the laundry room.
[The seeker reappears.]
We need to hurry up and find it.
Hurry up and find it!
Because I’ve been hiding in the same spot,
it feels like I’m making this game boring.
But, if I come out, it’s going to be too scary
and I’ll absolutely regret it afterwards.
[ANTON →]
I should definitely stay here.
[Ready or not,]
[here I come.]
What was that? What was that?
Hide, hide.
We need to hide.
[The seeker reappears.]
Can you stay with me?
Yeah, sure. Come here.
[WONBIN and SUNGCHAN enter the same room.]
[SHOTARO is all by himself in another room.]
[Ready or not.]
[EUNSEOK heads to the basement cafeteria.]
Am I allowed to hide here?
I’m hiding in the cafeteria kitchen...
Hey, hey, hey. Get out, get out.
I want to stay here.
[Ready or not,]
[two seekers are coming to get you.]
[There are two seekers.]
Two seekers?
I’m doomed.
[Are you done hiding?]
[I’m coming to get you now.]
[SUNGCHAN, SHOTARO and WONBIN are located on the 4th floor.]
[Half of the members are hiding on the 4th floor.]
This is a bad place to hide.
[No decent places to hide inside the room.]
[Eventually chooses the closet to hide in.]
Oh my, I can hear my heartbeat.
Ah…I’m really scared. I don’t think I can do this anymore.
SHOTARO!
Ah… should I just surrender?
Ah.
I’m like really scared.
Ha… I’m really scared. I don’t think I can do this anymore
[Sound of WONBIN swallowing.]
It’s scarier hiding inside the room.
[WONBIN leaves the room. ]
Should I just make it obvious and stay like this?
[Can they still be alive till the end?]
[ANTON and the seeker are located on the 1st floor.]
[The Seeker appears on the 1st floor.]
Please, please, please. Don’t come here.
[Enters the room ANTON is hiding in.]
[ANTON →]
[Leaves without noticing him.]
[ANTON’s sigh.]
Hiding in this spot is hard work.
Ha… it’s so uncomfortable.
[SUNGCHAN, WONBIN, SHOTARO and the seeker are located on the 4th floor. ]
[The second seeker is on the 4th floor.]
I hear the seeker.
[← SHOTARO]
[← SUNGCHAN]
[WONBIN →]
It’s close by.
It’s around here.
[Passes by SHOTARO.]
[← SUNGCHAN]
[WONBIN →]
[WONBIN, in the laundry room at the end of the hallway]
[Sound of the seeker’s cane.]
[WONBIN, SUNGCHAN, SHOTARO and the seeker are located on the 4th floor. ]
[← SUNGCHAN]
[→ WONBIN]
(Shh..)
[The seeker slowly approaches the laundry room.]
[WONBIN. I found you!]
Ah… this is terrifying. I don’t want to do this anymore.
WONBIN
got captured just now.
Ha… if we were together, I also would’ve…
[Sound of the seeker’s cane.]
been taken.
[SOHEE and EUNSEOK are located on B1.]
[Meanwhile on B1.]
[EUNSEOK exists the kitchen.]
[← EUNSEOK]
[SOHEE →]
This is too much. I’m scared.
To tell you the truth, I was really scared earlier.
I hear something.
[The seeker enters the basement cafeteria.]
[The seeker →]
[EUNSEOK →] [The seeker →] [SOHEE →]
(Lights turned off)
[While the seeker is searching the cafeteria, ]
[SOHEE’s phone alarm goes off.]
[The phone alarm breaks the silence.]
[SOHEE ↓] [EUNSEOK ↓]
[The seeker ↑]
[EUNSEOK runs to the other side.]
[The seeker notices EUNSEOK and chases after him.]
[EUNSEOK. I found you!]
Ahh! That was scary.
EUNSEOK got captured
and I could’ve been
captured because of my phone
but thanks to EUNSEOK
I didn’t get caught.
The seeker might come here again
because my phone alarm went off, right?
You got captured again?
Yea, it was scary getting caught.
It’s really scary when you hide with the door closed.
Yea, true.
[Current survival rate of RIIZE is about 66.67% ]
[SUNGCHAN, SHOTARO and the seeker are located on the 4th floor.]
[Sound of the door opening.]
The seeker is opening the doors.
[Moves to another room.]
[SHOTARO →]
[SHOTARO is hiding here.]
The seeker is here.
(Please, don’t come here.)
(Please.)
[Leaves without noticing SHOTARO.]
[Sound of the seeker knocking on the door.]
(The seeker is right next to me.)
[SUNGCHAN, SHOTARO and the seeker are located on the 4th floor.]
[The gap between them is gradually closing in.]
[The seeker arrives in front of the room SUNGCHAN is hiding in.]
[Sound of the seeker’s cane.]
[The seeker searches every corner of the room.]
[Here you are?]
[SUNGCHAN. I found you!]
Ah! you scared me.
Someone got captured next door.
Phew… this is tiring.
[← SHOTARO]
[SHOTARO’s phone alarm goes off. ]
Hey, this is WONBIN.
I’m in prison with EUNSEOK.
Do you have a key?
I do have one.
[In the meantime, SUNGCHAN arrives in prison.]
To avoid getting captured,
you need to come now with the key.
Okay, don’t call me anymore.
[Before heading over to the prison
SHOTARO searches for the key.]
Where is it?
It is definitely in this room.
Seriously, where is it?
Come on, I searched everywhere and it’s still not here?
[Hint for the key.]
[The laundry room on the 4th floor.]
[Rereading the hint.]
What is this?
[A hole in the ceiling.]
Oh!
I found it!
[Found the last key.]
I found the two keys
I’m coming to rescue you guys.
Hold on guys,
I’m coming to get you out.
Did we use up 3 keys in total so far?
[Currently used 4 keys in total.]
He’s here.
[SHOTARO arrives in prison.]
You have one more key?
Don’t save me! I’m too scared to come out.
[3 people are locked up
and there are 2 keys.]
I’ll save EUNSEOK and SUNGCHAN.
[EUNSEOK and SUNGCHAN are rescued.]
SHOTARO, you rescued two people?
I’m scared.
[SHOTARO, EUNSEOK, SUNGCHAN and SOHEE are located on B1.]
[Heads to the cafeteria right next to the prison.]
SOHEE, do you have a key?
No, I don’t!
SOHEE doesn’t have it.
You don’t have the key?
We just need to stay alive for 10 minutes.
Oh, no...
[RIIZE used all 6 keys.]
Is it safe to walk around together?
Of course it’s not.
What are they thinking? It’s not a good idea to stick together.
What are they up to now?
Ah... 9 minutes remaining.
Because there are 5 people not in prison…
we won.
[ Timer for 20 minutes.]
Ah… I’m locked up here for good.
[Time’s up for 20 minutes.
WONBIN is unable to escape now.]
It’s coming, coming, coming.
The seeker’s coming?
I can hear the seeker’s cane.
[Sound of the seeker’s cane.]
Hide over here.
[EUNSEOK hiding behind the food storage room door.]
[SUNGCHAN heads to the corner of the cafeteria.]
[↑ SHOTARO] [SOHEE →]
[← EUNSEOK]
[SUNGCHAN ↓]
[SHOTARO enters the kitchen.]
[At the same time, the seeker enters the cafeteria.]
[The seeker →]
[← SUNGCHAN] [The seeker →]
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
[SUNGCHAN. I found you!]
I shouldn’t have come out.
[Phone alarm goes off.]
[Remaining time is 444 seconds.]
[The seeker’s shadows, quicker than the seekers,]
[are on their way to find you.]
[The seeker’s shadows arrive
along with a disturbing noise.]
Huh?
What was that? Was that the seeker’s voice?
What was that? What was that?
[Sound of the shadows moving quickly.]
The shadows are starting to move.
[The shadows roaming around the 1st floor. ]
(Shuts his eyes. )
[Enters the room where ANTON is in.]
[Closely approaches ANTON. ]
[Leaves without noticing him.]
[With no luck, moves on to the next room.]
[ANTON sniffs his nose.]
I want to go home.
[SHOTARO, EUNSEOK, the seeker and SOHEE are located on B1.]
[The shadows go downstairs to the basement cafeteria.]
It’s here. It’s here. It’s here. It’s here.
[The roaring of the shadows.]
[Discovers SOHEE who was hiding.]
[SOHEE →]
[The shadows surround SOHEE.]
[Loudly summon the other seekers.]
[SOHEE quickly escapes.]
[The seeker immediately approaches.]
[SOHEE screaming.]
[The seeker ↓]
[The seeker ↓] [SOHEE ↓]
[Eventually, they run into each other.]
[SOHEE. I found you!]
But, we can’t save him because we ran out of keys...
[Current survival rate is 50%.]
[EUNSEOK →]
[EUNSEOK hiding in the food storage room.]
[The sound of the shadows getting closer.]
[The seeker and the shadow
both enter the food storage room.]
[Finds EUNSEOK behind the door]
[but just leaves.]
[EUNSEOK laughing.]
Why are they just leaving?
[There’s no way for them to just pass by.]
[EUNSEOK. I found you!]
[Current survival rate is 33.33%.]
Hey, call everyone!
Call SHOTARO.
SHOTARO doesn’t have the keys either.
Or call ANTON.
[The remaining time left for hide-and-seek is 100 seconds.]
I think it’s obvious that we lost the game.
[There’s no other method to increase the survival rate.]
It’s over?
Why did you get captured?
Did we lose the game?
We lost. More than 50% of the people are locked in here.
[Come out, come out wherever you are!]
[End of hide-and-seek.]
Is it over? Is it really over?
[ANTON finally comes out from the hiding spot.]
[Heads over to meet the rest of the members.]
[SHOTARO heads over to the prison.]
It’s over. It’s really over.
It’s over. It’s over.
We lost.
We lost because WONBIN didn’t come out of the prison.
But honestly what was ANTON doing this whole time?
[The youngest disappeared right when the game started.]
He never came out during the game.
I never saw him once.
Wow, ANTON is a true legend.
[ANTON finally appears.]
Hey ANTON, what were you doing?
ANTON, you never came out?
Looking at your hair, I guess you never did.
You were sleeping right?
In fact, I even called him
and he didn't say a word!
I know!
You did call me but the seeker was right outside.
I thought we would definitely win because
SHOTARO saved 2 people.
I thought I would never get caught but
the shadow flipped the chair.
(I screamed like this.)
I quickly escaped
and ran up the stairs to get away
but the seeker was coming towards me like this from upstairs.
[Phone alarm goes off.]
Oh, a message came.
[Because the survival rate was less than 50%,
the chance to present BRIIZE with some treats is now gone.]
I had no courage to save anyone.
It’s fine. It was really scary anyway.
[The seeker’s terrifying scream.]
- Hold on!
- That scared me!
[One more round?]
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]